{"_id": "1f225e8f", "question": "What is the last stroke Trump will make before leaving the White House?", "answers": "I envision trump's final insult to the American citizens and the Presidency will be the following ;\nAfter the Inauguration President Joe Biden and the First Lady will , with much fanfare and media coverage , set foot into the White House to begin his term as POTUS . Unbeknownst to all but a few , trump (who had refused to attend the Inauguration ceremony) has been hiding in the White House for the entire day and evading Secret Service agents who were trying to find him then escort him from the grounds . Just as the Bidens walk into the oval office , trump jumps out from his hiding place behind a curtain and drops trou exposing his immense Super Moon . He then attempts to run , maniacally cackling “ Nya nya…you can't catch me…I'm never leaving…I won , I won , I won “ . Unfortunately for the former President his humongous trousers and his Depends have bunched around his ankles and he falls face down-ass up… at which point he is corralled by the angry Secret Service detail . They then haul him out the front doors of the White House , pants still at his ankles...his giant pasty ass exposed to the January chill as well as all of the cameras of the main stream media …..all the while screaming at the top of his lungs , “ Take your hands off of me peasant…I won , I won the election ! I AM THE KING OF THE UNITED STATES , DAMMIT “ .\nDayum….if only ! That'd be some funny shit\n………………….… A QUICK UPDATE ………………..\nThe original comment (above) was posted on December 3 . This update posted on December 8 .\nI originally posted this (humorous ?) scenario about 5 days ago . I was quite surprised that in that short period of time it's received 13,000+ views . Equally surprising (to me , in any case) is that of all of those views this attempt at humor has only gotten about 40 upvotes . I can only assume that this must have pissed off quite a few folks . To anyone that has been offended I just want to say (borrowing the phrase from Steve Martin) ; Well , excuuuuse me ! LMAO\nBTW ; Thanks for the upvotes for those of you that did appreciate the humor . /;-{>"}
{"_id": "d5309e0d", "question": "When an MRI scan shows a little white, too small to be called a stroke, do the axons in that region die?", "answers": "I'll try to answer this, but I admit I've read no recent literature on the topic, so this response is at least a decade out of date.\nPunctuate T2 hyperintense “spots” are occasionally seen on MRI scans. They correlate with age and hypertension. When small in number and uniformly small in size, their significance is uncertain. “I read somewhere” (20 Years ago) that microscopic, post-mortem analysis of such lesions revealed - nothing.\nA few neuroradiologists Are on Quora And may have something to add. I'll defer to them.\nHyperintensity"}
{"_id": "e1154e47", "question": "Why are my Adobe Illustrator path strokes not completely solid? White patches are appearing randomly throughout the path's stroke.", "answers": "Hi Mohammed,\nDo path strokes appear similar to these examples above? If yes you need to look at Stroke dialog box in Illustrator.\nCommand + function key 10, or with Mouse cursor Window on main menu bar, scroll down to Stroke. This will open or close Stroke dialog box.\nSelect a path. Examine the stroke dialog box. Be sure the show option is on for the stroke dialog box. (little icon of three lines in right upper corner)\nIf dashed line is checked, uncheck it and see what happens to the selected path.\nThe next dialog box to examine is the Appearance, use the menu (little icon of three lines in right upper corner) in this dialog box and scroll to clear appearance. Observe what happens to selected path.\nRemember you have to select it to effect it.\nIf those do not change path “stokes not completely solid” issue. View the path in outline mode, make sure it is a one segment path and not many small path segments.\nIf none of these suggestions work, maybe another will have answer."}
{"_id": "8766c529", "question": "Why do villains stroke white cats in Hollywood films?", "answers": "The trope\noriginated with Cardinal Richelieu, a real historical person who was adapted as the villain of Alexandre Dumas’s classic novel The Three Musketeers and also really loved cats. However, almost all modern examples are references to James Bond’s archnemesis, the supervillain terrorist kingpin Ernst Stavro Blofeld. There are, however, a few film examples that predate Blofeld’s popularization of the trope, including (paradoxically) the animal-hating Disney villainess Cruella de Ville."}
{"_id": "445b1fba", "question": "Is it normal for a new 4-stroke bike to release white smoke?", "answers": "It is common for a freshly started from cold engine to release white vapour, especially on cold mornings. It is actually water vapour from moisture evaporating off from the inside of the exhaust.\nThe only time it is an issue is if the engine is water-cooled and it continually emits vapour coinciding with a drop in engine coolant… That generally signifies the head gasket has failed….."}
{"_id": "1f436db9", "question": "Is it true that if we eat white pepper powder it will be absorbed into our bloodstreams and get clogged in our capillaries resulting in increasing the chances of getting a stroke?", "answers": "Why only white pepper powder? Why not cornstarch and wheat flour and baking soda and the really fine salt they put on roasted nuts?\nBecause digestion doesn’t work that way. Humans are not amoebas that surround their food and take it inside their bodies. We have a separate system that extracts chemicals we need from the food we eat, moves those chemicals (not particles) into our bloodstream, and uses them to create energy, proteins, blood cells, whatever we need to survive.\namoeba hunting and ingesting paramecium (not how humans do it)"}
{"_id": "f323ad20", "question": "Which color is best as stroke around brand name in logo? White or...", "answers": "With the light blue they used, I thought it worked, There are definitely times when strokes look horrible (white stroke with black font isn't the coolest). Then again take Coca-Cola, their brand is in white and look how great it works for them (even though they can't use it all the time because it's white and white is hard to see with certain colors)."}
{"_id": "9329a10d", "question": "Does increasing the stroke of the engine change compression?", "answers": "Realize that unless you have a “really weird” engine to start with, it’s not possible to change ONLY the stroke length without also having to change other parts. For instance: if you lengthen stroke without also changing either the connecting rod length or the piston compression height (distance from the wrist pin centerline to the top of the piston) - or both, the longer stroke is going to cause the top of the piston to travel higher in the cylinder bore than it did before. Really bad things (as in “crossing the streams bad”) happen when a piston crashes into the bottom of the cylinder head and/or valves, so either you have to move those parts farther away from the piston tops or you have to ‘shorten’ the overall length of the piston/rod assembly. Compression ratio is nothing more than the ratio of the maximum volume (piston at bottom dead center- BDC) to the minimum cylinder volume (piston at top dead center - TDC) including the volume in the combustion chamber, head gasket opening, any valve reliefs in the pistons, etc. A longer stroke makes the maximum volume larger. If you shorten the piston/rod assembly so that it still fits into the cylinder at TDC without crashing into things, then assuming that the minimum volume is still near what it was before (piston height in the bore is the same as before) then viola - more compression because of the ratio. If you solved the interference problem by moving the fixed parts farther away (by using much thicker head gaskets for example) then resultant compression still depends on that ratio of max volume to min volume."}
{"_id": "039ff0b8", "question": "How do I care for my husband who is 57 but a stroke left him functioning at about a 12-year old level.", "answers": "Hmmm... I am guessing here that you concern is not so much related to what he thinks about but instead related to his behavior. If not, why would you care if his thoughts are somewhat childish?\nSo, my recommendation is to confront the behavior you find is improper or irritating in a respectful manner. Don't attack his character. Instead appeal to that part of him that is a man.\nAnother thought is that his behavior might be, in part, a reaction to your treatment of him. I know that it is not uncommon for a wife to treat her husband as if she were his mother. I think it is somewhat understandable for moms who are in that parenting mode much of the day. But you are not his mom. I'm not saying this is you issue, but if the shoe fits wear it.\nI am speaking to you about what you can do, so it may sound like I am taking his side. I'm not - I think it is highly likely that his behavior at times seems childish (mine does, too, at times). But he didn't ask me for advice.\nOne final thought. I highly recommend a book by Emmerson Eggerichs titled, \"Love and Respect\". You might find it really helpful. It is good at explaining some basic differences about how men and women think and it contains many useful suggestions for how both of you can improve your marriage.\nGood luck and may God bless!"}
{"_id": "8f0f7463", "question": "How did Jack White feel about being grouped with the Strokes during the early 2000s rock revival?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "8acfba0f", "question": "What causes white smoke in two-stroke locomotive engines?", "answers": "Atomized diesel fuel that is hot but has not been ignited during the combustion cycle."}
{"_id": "e76ccf3d", "question": "Why is a bad guy (like Dr. Evil) always stroking a cat (white one in particular) in movies?", "answers": "It's a reference to the 1963 Bond film \"From Russia With Love\", in which the villain - Ernest Blofeld - doesn't have his face shown, but is only filmed from behind, stroking a cat."}
{"_id": "bc0aaa87", "question": "What should happen with the White House if the president had a stroke leaving him unable to speak and function?", "answers": "This situation would, most likely, result in the implementation of Section 4 of the 25th Amendment to the US Constitution. Per the terms of this section, if both the Vice President and a majority of the members of the president’s cabinet believe that the President of the United States is incapacitated (be it physically, mentally, or any other situation that they believe renders the president unable to do his or her job), they must notify the Speaker of the House of Representatives and the President pro tempore of the Senate that the president is incapacitated. As soon as they do that, the president is relieved of duty (but not removed from office) and the vice president becomes Acting President of the United States.\nOnce the disability (whatever it is) no longer exists (let’s assume the president goes through rehab as well as physical and occupational therapy to the point that he or she feels ready to go back to work), the president would then notify the Speaker and President pro tempore of his or her intention to resume the powers and duties of the presidency. Should the vp and cabinet not agree with the president that he or she is now functional, they would so notify the Speaker and President pro tempore within four days of the president’s declaration of fitness, at which time Congress would have to decide the situation. If both houses of Congress vote by a 2/3 majority that the president is still incapacitated, the VP remains Acting President.\nThis type of scenario has never been implemented since it was written into the US Constitution in 1967. Many scholars and historians (myself included) are of the conclusion that it should have been used in March, 1981 after Ronald Reagan was shot. However, Vice President George HW Bush was out of Washington at the time, and by the time he returned to DC, Reagan was already out of surgery with a strong prognosis, so Bush decided not to ask the cabinet to invoke this procedure.\nAs a piece of added info, Section 3 of the same amendment provides for a president voluntarily surrendering power to the VP by using the same notification procedure, if he or she knows a disability exists or is going to exist. This part has been used three times—once by Reagan in 1985 when he was having surgery, and twice by George W Bush (in 2002 and 2007, I think) when he was undergoing routine medical testing that required sedation for an hour or so."}
{"_id": "ca6cd9ee", "question": "What could be causing white exhaust smoke? My 4 Stroke ATV smokes until it warms up for about 4 minutes.", "answers": "It could be Blown Head Gasket (BHG) Cracked Head or Block Pulled Bolts. To confirm it use engine combustion leak test kit. It looks for carbon dioxide/Carbon monoxide in the headspace of the radiator and, if detected, reveals that combustion gases are getting into the coolant.\nSo it also means water is getting into the combustion chamber which is making the exhaust gases turn white.\nThe just pour fluid from the kit into clever rubber cone, it should fit most radiator openings and use the aspirator bulb to pull the radiator air thru the fluid if fluid changes colour then exhaust gases are present in the cooling system.\nMixing of water and exhaust gases means minimum engine gasket change. if the head is cracked then it has to be replaced."}
{"_id": "e6c6fdd9", "question": "What would Russia look like if by some stroke of luck the white army held out and eventually took down the leaders of the Bolsheviks?", "answers": "There would have been a series of Wars between the newly independent former Russian Sates such as Poland, Finland the Baltic Sates and the Caucus States. There would also be a long running insurgency within Russia since retaking the land from peasants and returning it to landlords repeatedly led to rebellion in White army rear areas."}
{"_id": "53463c00", "question": "What happened to black and white relations in America? I grew up on \"Three-Dog Night,\" \"Fat Albert,\" \"Different Strokes,\" \"The Cosby Show,\" \"Martin,\" \"In Living Color,\" These were all my favorite TV shows. How did we get so divided all of a sudden?", "answers": "“It takes considerable knowledge just to realize the extent of your own ignorance.”\n― Thomas Sowell\nRace relations have been influenced by bad college theories that under most recent (and worst) iteration came about in the late 90s to early 2000s. These theories were fed to society heavily by about 2010. I explain them in the below. I’ve been fighting these theories for 20 years.\nRudolph Jensen's answer to What is wrong with saying ‘all lives matter’?\nThese theories linked below this paragraph are sexist and racist. They are leading to massive problems when applied to society that we are seeing right now. Of course, the “woke” crowd doesn’t see it that way. The theories divide people into groups based on race, sex, sexual orientation, and gender then perpetually treat those groups differently. Some are grouped into perpetual oppressors and others perpetual victims. Racism is discriminating against different races based on color of skin. Racism is dynamic and not fixed to a simplistic narrative. Academia has a LOT of power and they teach these theories to others. Those people once taught go into journalism, teaching, activist groups, and politics. Virtue signaling and getting special victim status is intoxicating as it’s a “feel good” narrative and gives power to those pushing the narrative. This type of victimology lead to authoritarianism and hundreds of millions of deaths in the 20th century through Communism and Fascism. You’d think humans would learn but alas they often don’t want to think critically. The number one problem and threat in the Western World now is adherence to these theories.\nCritical race theory - Wikipedia\nPostmodernism - Wikipedia\nIntersectionality - Wikipedia\nSome quotes from Dr. Thomas Sowell - Wikipedia\n“Virtually no idea is too ridiculous to be accepted, even by very intelligent and highly educated people, if it provides a way for them to feel special and important. Some confuse that feeling with idealism.”\n― Thomas Sowell\n“Some of the biggest cases of mistaken identity are among intellectuals who have trouble remembering that they are not God.”\n― Thomas Sowell\n“Intellectuals may like to think of themselves as people who \"speak truth to power\" but too often they are people who speak lies to gain power.”\n― Thomas Sowell\n“It is amazing how many people think that they can answer an argument by attributing bad motives to those who disagree with them. Using this kind of reasoning, you can believe or not believe anything about anything, without having to bother to deal with facts or logic.”\n― Thomas Sowell\n“One of the painful signs of years of dumbed-down education is how many people are unable to make a coherent argument. They can vent their emotions, question other people's motives, make bold assertions, repeat slogans-- anything except reason.”\n― Thomas Sowell\n“What socialism\n, fascism and other ideologies of the left have in common is an assumption that some very wise people—like themselves—need to take decisions out of the hands of lesser people, like the rest of us, and impose those decisions by government fiat.”\n― Thomas Sowell\nDo we really want children learning what’s shown in the video below? They are teaching “woke” theories in many schools across the country now. I learned about them in college.\nI am not pushing a narrative but rather I’m appealing to the reader to think critically about the narratives pushed upon society. Do not fall for “feel good” ideas with no substance.\nThe speaker below is in the UK parliament and is discussing the very issue I am writing about."}
{"_id": "5872a57f", "question": "Is it okay if steam or white smoke comes out of a two-stroke engine?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "978c063f", "question": "What causes white smoke in two stroke locomotive engines?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "8875e378", "question": "How do I know what is causing white flakes to fall from my head when I stroke my hand through my hair?", "answers": "It could also be caused by psoriasis. I have it and it and at times my scalp flakes. If you also have pitted fingernails this could be the reason. They are another symptom as well as itchy scaly patches of skin elsewhere. Some people don't develop it until later on in life and it does run in families. A dermatologist can diagnoses you if this is the case and prescribe medicines to help you. For more severe cases an injectable biologic works wonders. I use Taltz once a month and my skin and hair are totally free of plaques. Best of luck."}
{"_id": "1d5c863a", "question": "How can diet high in healthful plant-based food reduce the risk of stroke?", "answers": "First.\nwhat is the risk of stroke? Would a 25% reduction in stroke risk actually mean anything? Too much salt and/or diabetes will increase the stroke risk measurably.\nthe Japanese eat a nice healthy diet and have very low heart disease. Goog I hear you say. But they have a high incidence of stroke due to the salt intake of their diet.\nswings and roundabouts."}
{"_id": "fe7e5666", "question": "Mri showed a white spot in my brain where the stroke occurred. What were the 4 other places I saw?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "69cdf8f6", "question": "Are swapping out eggs and white bread for oatmeal linked to a lowered stroke risk?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "71e4a82b", "question": "When black catches heat faster and leaves faster (opposite to white),why didn't people who live in hot areas and especially work under sun didn't evolve to have white skin to avoid sun strokes, and it only becomes more black under the sun?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "497beb1e", "question": "What if a 4-stroke bike spark plug's chimney is somewhat white and the rest has black soot on it?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "746dc78e", "question": "Do you know what causes migraines with stroke like symptoms? I sometimes get them, and no doctors can figure it out, but my migraines make my words sound like gibberish, with sometimes vision loss.", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "c76e50cf", "question": "If a person suffers a left hemisphere ischaemic stroke which severely damages the brain areas which process language, would their brain respond to the language of their formative years as distinct from that of their adopted country?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "340b0a5f", "question": "What does it mean if you have white matter lesions on your brain from an MRI but all other tests rule out stroke possibility, including an MRA, Doppler ultrasound, and echocardiogram?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "206c8079", "question": "What was Zuckerberg's greatest stroke of genius?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "7cb67658", "question": "How are white spots on a brain MRI differentiated? How are strokes determined in compassion to calcification?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "ee23200f", "question": "How do I convince my widowed friend to stop wearing white saree without hurting her feelings? It has been 3 days since her husband suddenly died of stroke. She is depressed and refusing to wear any colorful clothes. She is 24 and married last year.", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "129d35aa", "question": "Why is Indie Rock so pretentious and so bland now, as compared to about 15 years ago when it was energetic and fun (bands like The Strokes, Hives, and White Stripes)? Did Pretentious Indie art rock music and snobby hipsters kill Rock and Roll music?", "answers": "I’m not sure I understand where you’re coming from when you say this. For one The Strokes are still around and still quite good, and there are many exhilarating, unpretentious, and original artists in the scene.\nIf by indie rock you mean that stuff they play on the “alternative” FM station…well I say that’s not really indie, but rather “alt-lite” stuff that has regrettably pushed its way to the mainstream by masquerading as something different to the masses while being quite passé to those of us with discerning ears. (Okay, maybe that’s a little bit harsh, but even the best stuff out of that bunch is still overrated as hell.)\nIf you haven’t already, I highly suggest you check out the following artists, among others:\nCourtney Barnett\nLand of Talk\nBroken Social Scene\nSt. Vincent\nThe War on Drugs\nWolf Parade\nAlvvays\nWarpaint\nReal Estate\nBeck (yes, he’s still around, and if Colors is any indication he’s as good as ever)\nThat’s just what’s been in my playlists lately — there’s so much more. If you find you like it, great! If not, then we’ll just have to agree to disagree.\nCheers!"}
{"_id": "e0dc66d5", "question": "Why don’t you pay someone to clear the snow? I know I do. There is less risk of a heart attack or stroke that way.", "answers": "Health insurance is good to have for this very reason.\nThe best health insurance is to stay strong, happy and healthy.\nClearing snow and sweeping up is top notch exercise.\nInviting strangers to do odd jobs usually means a risk to both parties. Again are you insured for these risks and the liabilities which may ensue if you are let down somehows in the quality of the work or behaviour of your casual labourer [1]?\nFootnotes\n[1] How should I trust strangers in my home or working around me I never met before and don't know?"}
{"_id": "44f8b20f", "question": "How does more melanin protect black people from sun damage? Black absorbs more than white so the darker your skin, the more of the sun's energy you absorb causing more skin damage and overheating causing heat stroke more.", "answers": "https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc...\nJ Physiol\n. 1955 Feb 28; 127(2): 236–246.\nPMCID: PMC1365770\nRelative efficiency of pigment and horny layer thickness in protecting the skin of Europeans and Africans against solar ultraviolet radiation\n*\nM. L. Thomson\nBasically this study found that dark skin people are not only darker, but their skin is hotter, however melanin disperses the heat, which also prevents burns. Dark skin (in this case SubSaharan Africans) can absorb nearly 36% more solar radiation than indigenous Europeans (on average)…obviously all African and all Europeans are not of the same skin color. This absorption of greater heat, they found to increase the quickness at which Africans began to sweat compared to Europeans, which helped cool them faster.\nBack in the 1950’s some people thought black people just had “thicker skin” and therefore this gave them more immunity to sunlight than Europeans. However , that was found not to matter. It was melanin. Melanin disperses solar radiation, stopping it from damaging the skin tissues, this is found to more than compensate for the fact it actually absorbs more solar radiation.\nThis is actually counter intuitive…I suppose. White people burn although their skin is more reflective. Black people have far less reflective skin, but the thing that makes the skin less reflective is also what protects it from solar radiation…amazing!"}
{"_id": "7f8793ed", "question": "After going red during heat stress, then white and clammy at heat exhaustion, what causes the skin go red again during the progression from heat exhaustion to heat stroke?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "fab3e43d", "question": "If you play in a 2-person best ball tournament and use senior and white tees, do you adjust the handicap by the difference in course rating as the USGA rule is for stroke play?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "74325c50", "question": "When I use the eyedropper in illustrator it changes my stroke to white. How do I change this?", "answers": ""}
